sparkloaded.com 2018-04-26

# Privacy Policy – SparkLoaded

### 

### **Privacy Policy for** [http://www.sparkloaded.com](http://www.sparkloaded.com/)

The privacy of our visitors to [**http://www.sparkloaded.com**](http://www.sparkloaded.com/) is important to us.

At **[http://www.sparkloaded.com](http://www.sparkloaded.com/),** we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit **SparkLoaded** and how we safeguard your information.

NOTE:- We never sell your personal information to third parties.

Log Files As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Globacom Nigeria), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer, Safari or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

Cookies and Web Beacons This blog doesn’t use cookies. However, some of our business partners (for example, advertisers) may use cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers.

The information we collect including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing Lagos Real Estate ads to someone in Lagos, Nigeria, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing mobile phones ads to someone who frequents Phone sites).

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.
